<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>https://techxero.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>info@techxero.com (💻TechXero💻)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>info@techxero.com (💻TechXero💻)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://techxero.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Major Refactor</title>
      <link>https://techxero.com/posts/refactor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>info@techxero.com (💻TechXero💻)</author>
      <guid>https://techxero.com/posts/refactor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-design&#34;&gt;New Design&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After rocking the same old, now &lt;em&gt;deprecated&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Hugo Theme&lt;/strong&gt; for what feels like forever, I finally decided it’s time to shake things up. I switched to a theme that’s still actively maintained. Sure, it might not be as flashy or &lt;em&gt;sexy&lt;/em&gt; as the old one, but man, it’s way easier to keep in shape.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’m a big fan of &lt;strong&gt;Hugo&lt;/strong&gt;, so no chance I’m ever dropping it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube</title>
      <link>https://techxero.com/posts/channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>info@techxero.com (💻TechXero💻)</author>
      <guid>https://techxero.com/posts/channel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;information&#34;&gt;Information&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’m excited to share that I have created a brand new &lt;strong&gt;YouTube Channel&lt;/strong&gt; where I will be uploading &lt;em&gt;IRL Updates&lt;/em&gt;, real, unfiltered moments from my life. I’ve already uploaded the very first video, and I want to be honest with you: making that video was incredibly challenging. It wasn’t just about hitting the record button, it was about opening up and talking about some uncomfortable, deeply personal subjects. In doing so, I really laid myself bare, exposing parts of my story that I don’t usually share.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This channel is more than just a place for videos; it’s a space where I hope to connect on a genuine level, to be vulnerable, and to explore life’s ups and downs with all of you. I appreciate your support as I take this journey, and I can’t wait to share more real moments with you along the way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Read on to know more&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
